A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Administrative Files, RG 1 FA427
Rockefeller Archive Center
Asian Cultural Council records, Administrative Files, RG 1
1952-2006
Rockefeller Archive Center
JDR 3rd Fund
Asian Cultural Council
FA427
115.71 Cubic Feet RG 1 currently comprises 247 document boxes.
Record Group 1 comprises 246 document boxes.
Separated Materials
Special Formats (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) are being separated from the body of the collection. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 15 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Record Group 1: Administrative is arranged in three subgroups as follows:
SG 1: ACC records of the JDR 3rd Fund
SG 2: ACC records
SG 3: Financial
Each subgroup is further arranged primarily by record type.
Biographical / Historical
The Asian Cultural Council (ACC) is an organization that fosters the development of Asian artists.
Originally, part of the JDR 3rd Fund, the Asian Cultural Program was a program which was created in 1963. Growing up, John D. Rockefeller 3rd got his love of art and Asia from both his parents, JDR Jr. and Abby Rockefeller. JDR 3rd saw a need to have an exchange between Asia and the United States in the Arts; visual, performing, the humanities, in which he created the JDR 3rd Fund. After the passing of JDR 3rd in 1978, the Asian Cultural Program became its own organization with support from the JDR 3rd Fund and private donors; the Asian Cultural Council was created in 1980, which continued to fund the Asian Arts and artists. ACC's philosophy on their success is their unique program on cultural exchange in carefully selecting those individuals, closely advising them, and providing them with a peerless level of personal and intensive programming. Their grants have gone to over 25 countries in Asia and in twenty different fields of Arts. They also help fund organizations and educational institutions in the United States and Asia for research, study, and creative work within the United States and Asia. Their headquarters are in New York City but have offices in Hong Kong, Tokyo, Manila, and Taipei.
Scope and Contents
Records include: Correspondence, reports, administrative records, grant submissions, meeting minutes, newspaper articles, photographs and gallery catalogs.
International relations -- United States; Education; International relations; Japan; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations; Hong Kong; Asia; Charities -- Investments; Charities; Arts; Humanities; Philanthropy; Charitable contributions
- Administrative, 1952, 1954-2006; 1; 108.25 Cubic Feet 246 document boxes.
  Related Materials
  JDR 3rd Fund, Ford Foundation, Rockefeller Foundation, Rockefeller Brothers Fund
  - ACC records of the JDR 3rd Fund, 1952, 1954-1955, 1957-1989; 1
    Scope and Contents
    Materials pertain to the administrative offices of the Asian Cultural Program at the JDR 3rd Fund and the early creation of the Asian Cultural Council.
    Records include: Correspondence, reports, administrative records, grant submissions, meeting minutes, newspaper articles, photographs, gallery catalogs, and other oversize material
    Arrangement
    Series 1: Board of Trustees Series 2: JDR 3rd Fund Series 3: Director's Office Series 4: Comptroller's Office Series 5: Trip Notes Series 6: International Council on Museums (ICOM) News Bulletin
    JDR 3rd Fund, Ford Foundation, Rockefeller Foundation
    - Board of Trustees, 1964-1980; 1
      - Agenda, Executive Committee Meeting, 1968 February 27 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1968 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Agenda, Executive Committee Meeting, 1968 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1969 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Agenda, Executive Committee Meeting, 1970 August 31 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1971 February 10 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1972 October 17 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1973 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1973 May 30 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Agenda, Executive Committee Meeting, 1974 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1974 May 22 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1974 October 3 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1975 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1975 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1976 June 10 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1976 October 21 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1977 May 11 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1977 October 12 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1978 May 16 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1978 October 13 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1979 May 4 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1979 October 19 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1980 May 30 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Agenda, Meeting, 1980 October 17 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Executive Committee Dockets, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Document of Record, Vol. 1 (Folder 1 of 2), 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Document of Record, Vol. 2 (Folder 1 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Document of Record, Vol. 3 (Folder 1 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Document of Record, Vol. 4 (Folder 1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Document of Record, Vol. 5 (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Document of Record, Vol. 6 (Folder 1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Document of Record, Vol. 7 (Folder 1 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - JDR 3rd Fund, 1952, 1954-1955, 1957, 1959-1961, 1963-1980, 1983; 2
      - Annual Register of Grants Support, 1975, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Annual Report, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Annual Report, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Annual Report, Grant List, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Annual Report: Text and Captions, 1974, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - Annual Report, Text and Grant Lists, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - Annual Report, Text and Grant Lists, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Annual Report: Text and Grant Lists, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - Apartments, 1967-1975 (Box 6, Folder 50)
      - Apartments, Broome St., Loft, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 51)
      - Apartments, Luten, 1976, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 52)
      - Articles, 1965-1966, 1969, 1971-1972, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 53)
      - Asian Cultural Program, Attachments A, B, and C, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 54)
      - Asian Cultural Program, Grant Commitments, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 55)
      - Asian Cultural Program Committee Memoranda, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 56)
      - Biographies, 1968, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 57)
      - Board Materials, 1967, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 58)
      - Board Materials, 1969-1971, 1973-1979 (Box 6, Folder 59)
      - Board Meeting, 1976 October 21 (Box 6, Folder 60)
      - Board Meeting, 1977 May 11 (Box 6, Folder 61)
      - Board Meeting, 1978 May 16 (Box 6, Folder 62)
      - Board Meeting, 1978 October 13 (Box 6, Folder 63)
      - Certification for Payment, Asian Cultural Program Individual, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 64)
      - Certification for Payment, Asian Cultural Program Individual, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 65)
      - Certification for Payment, Asian Cultural Program Individual, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 66)
      - Certification for Payment, Asian Cultural Program Institutional, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 67)
      - Certification for Payment, Asian Cultural Program Institutional, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 68)
      - Certification for Payment, Asian Cultural Program Institutional, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 69)
      - Charter & By Laws, 1970, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 70)
      - Committee on Future of Asian Cultural Program, Minutes, 1978-1978 (Box 7, Folder 71)
      - Copies of Correspondence and Memoranda, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 72)
      - Copies of Correspondence and Memoranda, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Copies of Correspondence and Memoranda, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Docket Materials, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Docket Materials, 1976 June (Box 8, Folder 76)
      - Equipment & Materials, by Country, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 77)
      - Executive Committee, 1968, 1976, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 78)
      - Executive Committee Meetings, Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 79)
      - Exhibitions Related to Japan, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 80)
      - Ford Foundation: Asia, Lisa Lyons, 1974, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 81)
      - Foundations, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Four Year Report Acknowledgments, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - General Administrative, 1976, 1978, 1982-1986, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - General Correspondence, 1959-1961, 1964, 1966-1970, 1972, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - General Correspondence, 1963-1970, 1974-1975, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - General Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1955, 1957, 1967-1964, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - General Correspondence, Sponono, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 88)
      - Grant Listings, 1964-1980 (Box 9, Folder 89)
      - Grant Requests, Equipment, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Grant Support Related to Japan, Other Than JDR 3rd Fund, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Grants, Indonesia, Copies, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Grants, Indonesia, Drafts and Notes, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Grants, Japan, 1972 June (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Grants for Asian Cultural Activities, Afghanistan-India, 1964-1978 (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Grants for Asian Cultural Program, Indonesia-Nepal, 1964-1978 (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Grants for Asian Cultural Program, Pakistan-Asia General, 1964-1978 (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Grants for India, Drafts and Notes, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 98)
      - Grants Related to Japan, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 99)
      - Interoffice, Rockefeller Offices, 1964-1968, 19790, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Interoffice, Smith, Datus C., Jr., 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Interoffice, Smith, Datus C., Jr., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Interoffice, Smith, Datus C., Jr., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 103)
      - Interoffice, Smith, Datus C., Jr., 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 104)
      - Interoffice, Staff, 1973, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 105)
      - JDR 3rd, Asia Trips, 1960s, 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 106)
      - JDR 3rd, Asia Trips, 1970s, 1971, 1975-1976, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 107)
      - JDR 3rd and Grantee Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 108)
      - JDR 3rd Fund Formation, 1964-1965, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 109)
      - JDR 3rd Speeches, 1950s, 1952, 1954, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 110)
      - JDR 3rd Speeches, 1960s, 1960, 1964-1965, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 111)
      - JDR 3rd Speeches, 1970s, 1970-1972, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 112)
      - Letters of Condolence, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 113)
      - Meetings with Grantees, 1976 Fall (Box 10, Folder 114)
      - Organizational Matters, Annual Report, Correspondence, 1966-1968, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 115)
      - Press Clippings, 1963, 1968, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 116)
      - Press Clippings, 1965-1972, 1974, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 117)
      - Press Clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 118)
      - Report Distribution Lists, 1963-1967 (Box 11, Folder 119)
      - Rockefeller, Meile, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 120)
      - Search Committee, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 121)
      - Staff Meetings, 1972-1976, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 122)
      - Supporting Materials for FY 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 123)
      - Tax Exemption, 1964-1965, 1970, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 124)
      - Thailand, Bronze Conservation, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 125)
      - Trustee Meeting, 1973 October 11 (Box 11, Folder 126)
      - Trustee Meeting Notes, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 127)
      - Trustees, 1961-1964, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 128)
      - 12-Year Report, 1972-1978 (Box 11, Folder 129)
    - Director's Office, 1955, 1957-1989; 3
      Subseries 1: Asian Educational Institutions Subseries 2: Asian Foundations Subseries 3: Asian Government Subseries 4: Asian Individuals Subseries 5: Asian Libraries Subseries 6: Asian Museums Subseries 7: Asian Organizations Subseries 8: Countries Subseries 9: Other Foundations Subseries 10: Other Governments Subseries 11: Other Individuals Subseries 12: Other Museums Subseries 13: Other Organizations Subseries 14: Other Universities Subseries 15: U. S. Educational Institutions Subseries 16: U. S. Foundations Subseries 17: U. S. Government Subseries 18: U. S. Individuals Subseries 19: U. S. Libraries Subseries 20: U. S. Museums Subseries 21: U. S. Organizations
      - Asian Educational Institutions, 1963-1984, 1986-1987; 1
        - Afghanistan, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 130)
        - Bangladesh, General, 1968, 1973-1977 (Box 12, Folder 131)
        - Bangladesh, University of Dacca, 1968, 1972-1973, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 132)
        - Cambodia, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 133)
        - Hong Kong, 1968-1975, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 134)
        - India, General, 1963-1971, 1973, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 135)
        - India, Birla Academy of Art & Culture, 1965-1970, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 136)
        - India, Birla Institute of Technology & Science, 1973-1974, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 137)
        - India, Calcutta School of Music, 1967-1968, 1970, 1972-1975 (Box 12, Folder 138)
        - India, Delhi University, 1965, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 139)
        - India, M. S. University of Baroda, 1963-1966, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 140)
        - India, National Institute of Design (Folder 1 of 2), 1966-1973, 1975-1980, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 141)
        - India, National Institute of Design (Folder 2 of 2), 1966-1973, 1975-1980, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 142)
        - India, School of Architecture, Ahmedabad, 1968-1972 (Box 13, Folder 143)
        - Indonesia, ASRI (Akademi Seni Rupa Indonesia), 1972-1973, 1977, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 144)
        - Indonesia, Bandung Institute of Technology, 1967-1973 (Box 13, Folder 145)
        - Indonesia, Cenderawasih University, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 146)
        - Indonesia, General, 1968-1973, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 147)
        - Indonesia, Maktab Perguruan Ilmu Khas, 1969-1974 (Box 13, Folder 148)
        - Indonesia, National University, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 149)
        - Indonesia, University of Papua & New Guinea, 1968-1971 (Box 13, Folder 150)
        - Japan, General, 1964-1967, 1970, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 151)
        - Japan, General, 1964-1967, 1970, 1978; Oversized (Box 247, Folder 4706)
        - Korea, General, 1965-1967, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 152)
        - Korea, Seoul National University, 1964, 1967, 1970, 1972-1978 (Box 14, Folder 153)
        - Malaysia, Nepal, & Pakistan, General, 1968-1972, 1975, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 154)
        - Philippines, General, 1964, 1966-1968, 1970, 1973, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 155)
        - Philippines, Philippine Women's University, 1964, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 156)
        - Philippines, University of Philippines, Agbayani, Virginia, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 157)
        - Philippines, University of Philippines, Correspondence, 1965-1969, 1971-1972, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 158)
        - Philippines, University of Philippines, Printed Matter, 1966-1968, 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 159)
        - Singapore, General, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 160)
        - Taiwan, General, 1964-1965, 1968-1970, 1973, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 161)
        - Thailand, General (Folder 1 of 2), 1966-1975, 1977-1978, 1981-1982, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 162)
        - Thailand, General (Folder 2 of 2), 1966-1975, 1977-1978, 1981-1982, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 163)
      - Asian Foundations, 1961-1979, 1982; 2
        - General, 1968, 1970-1972, 1974-1979, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 164)
        - Bhakti Vidya Foundation, Indonesia, 1967, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 165)
        - Jajasan Mitra Budaja Indonesia, 1968-1972 (Box 15, Folder 166)
        - Philippines, 1969, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 167)
        - Magsaysay (Ramon) Award Foundation, Philippines, Correspondence, 1964-1970, 1972-1973, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 168)
        - Magsaysay (Ramon) Award Foundation, Philippines, Printed Materials, 1961-1966 (Box 15, Folder 169)
      - Asian Government, 1966-1975, 1978; 3
        - Bhutan, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 170)
        - Indonesia-West Irian, 1969-1971 (Box 15, Folder 171)
        - Micronesia-Mariana Islands, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 172)
        - Singapore, 1968-1969, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 173)
        - Sri Lanka, 1966-1969, 1972-1973, 1975, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 174)
        - Tibet, 1967-1969, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 175)
        - Vietnam, 1968, 1972, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 176)
      - Asian Individuals, 1955, 1957, 1959-1983; 4
        - A, 1964-1982
          - Abas, Abdul Aziz, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 177)
          - Abbas, Yavar, 1967, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 178)
          - Abbasi, Mustafa Zaman, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 179)
          - Abdi, Wahab, 1965, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 180)
          - Abe, Mario, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 181)
          - Abidin, Nik Zainal, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 182)
          - Abu Bakar, Tunku Zubeidah, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 183)
          - Abueva, Napoleon, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 184)
          - Achwal, Madhao Bhaskar, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 185)
          - Adachi, Masao (Box 16, Folder 186)
          - Adarme, Tommy C., 1972 (Box 16, Folder 187)
          - Adhyatmanses, T. K., 1976 (Box 16, Folder 188)
          - Affandi, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 189)
          - Agarwal, Jai Krishna, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 190)
          - Agrawal, Yashodhara, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 191)
          - Agrawala, Bharat Bhushan, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 192)
          - Agrawala, R. C., 1976 (Box 16, Folder 193)
          - Agung, A. A. G., 1972 (Box 16, Folder 194)
          - Ahmad, Razia Sultana, 1971, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 195)
          - Ahmed, Anna Molka, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 196)
          - Ahn, Kun-Hyuck, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 197)
          - Ahn, Suyon, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 198)
          - Ahn, Yong-ku, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 199)
          - Ahn, Young-ja, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 200)
          - Ahuja, Vinial, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 201)
          - Ai, Shu-lu, 1969, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 202)
          - Akashi, Yasushi, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 203)
          - Akatsuka, Ryusuke, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 204)
          - Akhlaq, Zahoor, 1976-1979 (Box 16, Folder 205)
          - Akhtar, Roohi, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 206)
          - Akiyama, Kuniharu, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 207)
          - Akutagwa, Hiroshi, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 208)
          - Alam, Ihtesham, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 209)
          - Alam, Nural, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 210)
          - Albakri, Hisham, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 211)
          - Albano, Raymundo R., 1972-1973, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 212)
          - Albano, Raymundo R., 1972-1973, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 212A)
            Conditions Governing Access
            Original materials are fragile, use with permission only
          - Alcuaz, Federico Aguilar, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 213)
          - Alegre, Ed, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 214)
          - Alejandro, Reynaldo, 1972-1973, 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 215)
          - Ali, Habib Fida, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 216)
          - Ali, Mehrab, 1974-1978 (Box 17, Folder 217)
          - Ali, Mohammed, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 218)
          - Ali, Zakaria Bin, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 219)
          - Amaldev, Jerry, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 220)
          - Amemiya, Yasukazu & Chu Lan (Gyokuran), 1974 (Box 17, Folder 221)
          - Amin, Vinoobhai B., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 222)
          - Amir, Hazim, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 223)
          - Amirthanayagam, Guy, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 224)
          - Amster, S. L., 1970 (Box 17, Folder 225)
          - Anaapillai, Kamadev, 1970-1973, 1974, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 226)
          - Ancheta, Augusto Sulse, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 227)
          - Ancheta, Augusto Sulse, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 227A)
            Restricted from scholarly access-Confidential material
          - Angsuthayanon, Utai, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 228)
          - Annand, Jeet, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 229)
          - Anoda, Afrizal, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 230)
          - Ansari, Mohammed S., 1975, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 231)
          - Ansarie, Jamshaed, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 232)
          - Antonio, Angelito, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 233)
          - Anuar, Rahman, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 234)
          - Anzai, Keiko, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 235)
          - Anziano, S., 1976 (Box 17, Folder 236)
          - Ao, Rongsen, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 237)
          - Aoyagi, Tadashi, 1977, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 238)
          - Appasamy, Jaya, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 239)
          - Aquino, Ruben A., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 241)
          - Arakawa, Shusaku, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 242)
          - Ariadne, Gudrajati, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 243)
          - Aribasam, Mohamad Aum, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 244)
          - Arif, Atjeng, 1969, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 245)
          - Arif, Atjeng, 1969, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 245A)
          - Arshizadah, Akbar Ali Khan, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 246)
          - Aruego, Jose, Jr., 1971 (Box 17, Folder 247)
          - Asaka, Yoshiko, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 248)
          - Asano, Hiroshi, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 249)
          - Asaranatana, Anant, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 250)
          - Atmowiloto, Arswendo, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 251)
          - Atreya, S. K., 1976 (Box 17, Folder 252)
          - Atri, M. C., 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 253)
          - Atsumi, Ikuko, 1969, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 254)
          - Atul, Patel, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 255)
          - Awazu, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 256)
          - Ayyangar, R. Rangarmanuja, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 257)
          - Ayyangar, V. Ranganayaki, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 258)
          - Aziz, Zulkifli, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 259)
          - Azraii, Zain, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 260)
        - B, 1965-1980
          - Bae, Yoong (Bae Chung Kook), 1969 (Box 17, Folder 261)
          - Bagh, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 262)
          - Baghaei, Razi, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 263)
          - Bahadur, P., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 264)
          - Bajpai, Rajendra, 1976-1978, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 265)
          - Bajpeyi, Ashok, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 266)
          - Bakti, Mohamed Noor, 1968, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 267)
          - Bala, Madhu, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 268)
          - Balasaraswati, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 269)
          - Banerjee, Bimal, 1967, 1969-1973, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 270)
          - Banerjee, Dipak, 1967-1972 (Box 18, Folder 271)
          - Banerjee, N. R., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 272)
          - Banerjee, Nikhil, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 273)
          - Bangdel, Lain S., 1968, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 274)
          - Barakat, Birjees, 1973, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 275)
          - Barot, Anand, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 276)
          - Basavarao, Mandalapu, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 277)
          - Benegal, Nira, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 278)
          - Beri, V. P., 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 279)
          - Bhalla, Jai Rattan, 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 280)
          - Bhatt, Markand, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 281)
          - Bhatt, Panubhai N., 1975 (Box 18, Folder 282)
          - Bhatt, Salil, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 283)